{
    "subject": "resource/Chris_Penn",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1965-10-10",
    "human_readable": "Chris Penn was born on October 10, 1965.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8495657444000244,
            "question": "October 10th of what year marks Chris Penn's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8112462759017944,
            "question": "When was Chris Penn born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7249147295951843,
            "question": "What day was Chris Penn born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6781930923461914,
            "question": "What is Chris Penn's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6452882289886475,
            "question": "What month was Chris Penn born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776448249816895,
            "question": "Is Chris Penn's birthdate in the fall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5253952145576477,
            "question": "How old is Chris Penn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43357303738594055,
            "question": "On which date did Chris Penn celebrate his first birthday?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36069491505622864,
            "question": "In what year did Chris Penn come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2087576687335968,
            "question": "If today is November 1st, 2023, how many days have passed since Chris Penn's birthday this year?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chris Penn was born on October 10, 1965.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6447_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Chris Penn come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6447_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On which date did Chris Penn celebrate his first birthday?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6447_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is Chris Penn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6447_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6447_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents contain multiple mentions of Chris Penn's birthdate as October 10, 1965."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Chris Penn was born on October 10, 1965. Therefore, the triple \"Chris Penn was born on October 10, 1965\" is correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}